Guide to the Thomas S. Foley Photographs 1905-1995
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Family and Political Photographs
  - Charles Bloom, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - President Ronald Reagan Joint Session Address with Vice President George H. W. Bush, Tip O'Neill, Trent Lott, Jim Wright, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Interns Bryce Quick and Willie Austin, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Glenn M. Anderson, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Inaugural address, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Sugar Users Group's Collequim in Phoenix, Arizona, 1981 February (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Egyptian President Omer Sadat, 1981 Spring (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Preping for Reagan's Inaugural Address, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - President Ronald Reagan's Address to Congress, 1981 February (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Kaiser Aluminum's "One Person Can Make a Difference" Award Banquet, 1981 February (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Inaugural Ceremonies at Whitworth College, 1981 Spring (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee Dinner, 1981 Spring (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Heather Foley with Mrs. Lott, Mrs. Miller, Mrs Rostenkowski, Mrs. Nancy Reagan, 1981 May (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Tax Proposal Meeting with House Leadership and President Ronald Reagan, 1981 July (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Nick Rahall's Birthday Party, 1981 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Sugar Ray Leonard and Tip O'Neill, 1981 September (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - William R. Cotter's Funeral, 1981 September (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - McCormack Award Ceremony, 1980 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Speaker Tip O'Neill and Intern Mary Driscoll, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Democratic House Leadership, Tip O'Neill at Luncheon for President Jimmy Carter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Vice President George H. W. Bush, 1981 November (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Bonneville Power's Earl Gjelbe and Larry Hittle, circa 1982 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Speakers Tip O'Neill, Jim Wright, Leadership, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Democratic Congressional Dinner, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Reception, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Leadership, President Ronald Reagan, Tip O'Neill at White House, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Senate Staffer Nordy Hoffman and Others, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Jackson and University of Washington Members, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Pacific Factors Ltd. Members, Seattle WA, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Being Fitted for Cougar Jacket at Washington State University, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - President Ronald Reagan, State of the Union Address, 1982 January 26 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Reception with Dayle Hennington, 1982 February (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Snowmobilers Convention at Cle Elum High School, 1982 February (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Tip O'Neill at Representative Jim Wright's Dinner Party, 1982 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Congressman George Danielson, 1982 February (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Fishing, 1982 March (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - "Business Executives on Federal Government Operations" Conference Hosted by Brookings Institute, 1982 March (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Eastern Washington University's Founders Day Celebration, 1982 May (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Advocating Right to Tape Legislation at International Consumer Electronics Show, 1982 Summer (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - US Capitol Police, McDonald and Family, 1982 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - World Forum in Vail, Colorado, 1982 August (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Breakfast Meeting with Susan Moos and Others at Howard University, 1982 September (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - M.C.H.S. Dedication, 1982 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - "Meet the Press", 1982 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Association of American Publishers, Inc., circa 1983 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Select Committee on Aging Hearings and Sewer Meeting with Maggie Scoop, circa 1983 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Sidney Poitier, circa 1983 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Hanford Nuclear Site, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Tip O'Neill and March of Dimes Child, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Bob Mariani of Portland State University, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Heather Foley with Henry Kissinger on Air Force One for Jackson's Funeral, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - US Air Force Academy Event in Denver, Colorado, 1983 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Phil Burton Memorial Service, 1983 Aprl 21 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Tip O'Neill at Guiness-Harp Corp. Capitol Concert, 1983 May (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - 20th Annual Democratic Congressional Dinner, 1983 May (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - President Ronald Reagan's Address to Congress regarding El Salvadore, 1983 May (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Grand Coulee Dam's 50th Anniversary, 1983 July (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Page Scott Kaden, 1983 Fall (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Heather Foley with Speaker Carl Albert, 1983 October (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Supreme Court Reception, circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Local Postmasters, Janet Stephens, circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Heather Foley with Speaker Carl Albert (Signed), circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Dinner Party, circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Ford Bronco Negative, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Travelling to Representative Clement Zablocki's Funeral, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - National Education Association's Sue Harch, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Tip O'Neill, Fritz, Mondale, and Dan Rostenkowski, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Heather Foley at Democratic National Convention, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Tip O'Neill on Airplane, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - State of the Union Address with President Ronald Reagan, 1984 January (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Electronic Industries Seminar in Las Vegas, Nevada, 1984 February (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - White House Briefing on Central America with President Ronald Reagan, 1984 February 3 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Greek Orthodox Archbishop Iakovos of North and South America, 1984 March (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - B'Nai B'rith Dinner, 1984 Spring (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Independent Bakers Association Award, 1984 June (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Food for Peace Bill Signing Ceremony with President Ronald Reagan and Leadership, 1984 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Unveiling of Speaker Tip O'Neill's Portrait, 1994 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - San Fransisco Barbecue with Jim Wright, Murtha, etc., 1984 October (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Werner Brandt, George Kundanis and Whip Staff, circa 1985 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Representatives Stallings and Coelho, circa 1985 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - James Stewart, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ashbrook Baking Co.'s Thomas Boge, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Jim and Mrs. Tribitt, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - President Jimmy Carter, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Phil Swink, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Art Exhibit, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Tip O'Neill at Bill Signing Event, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Representative Wright Making Announcement, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Representatives Michael, O'Neill, and Wright, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hadassah's Zmira Goodman and Ruth Popkin, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - President Ronald Reagan, Representatives Daniel Inouye and Alan Cranston, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Jose N. Duarte, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Washington State Delegation, Dicks, Pritchard, Lowry, Swift, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Representative Pat Schroeder, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Representatives Denny Miller, Sid Morrison, and Les Aspin, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mary Bitterman-Akaka, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Students, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Unknown School Groups, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - President Ronald Reagan (Signed), circa 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Far Eastern Textile Group, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 98th Congress New Freshmen Members, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Representative Soloman Ortiz Birthday Party, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce Annual Dinner, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - House Leadership, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Speaking at Podium, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - University of Washington Alumni Banquet, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bipartisan Congressional Leadership at White House, 1985 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Representative Gillis Long Funeral Services, 1985 February (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Meet the Press", 1985 February 10 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Grocers Association's "Spirit of America Award", 1985 March 12 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - F. Kemper Freeman, President of Bellevue Square Managers, at Congressional Contacts Meeting of International Council of Shopping Centers, circa 1985 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Whip meeting with House Leadership November 21, 1985, 1985 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Senator Alan K. Simpson, 1985 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Tip O'Neill, 1985 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Holocaust Memorial Center, 1985 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 99th Congressional Leadership Departure, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - President Jimmy Carter and Michael Apatoff, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Boxer Hearns (?), circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Representative Frank Annunzio, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Tip O'Neill, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Veteran's Day Event in Walla Walla, Washington, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Press Conference with Columbian President Barco, circa 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Columbian President Barco, circa 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Tip O'Neal and Minority Leader Robert Michel, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Parents Judge, Heather Foley, Tip O'Neal, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Receiving Patriot Award from Boy Scouts, circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - 99th Congress Freshmen members, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Tip O'Neill at Podium in Statuary Hall, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Tip O'Neill's Birthday Party, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Dog, Alice, at Humane Society, 5th District Washington, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Schwerin Farm, Walla Walla, Washington, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Shriners, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Personal Photos, Home, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - For Christmas Cards, Indoors and Fishing, with Heather Foley, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - For Christmas Cards, Outside, with Heather Foley, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Tip O'Neill's Retirement Party, 1986 January (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Center for National Policy Dinner, 1986 March (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bob Rubin, Roger Altman, C. Schumer, W. Brandt, 1986 March (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - National Leadership Forum with President Ronald Reagan, 1986 June (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Presidential Volunteer Award of the Year, Carol Sasaki, 1986 June (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, 1986 September (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, 1986 September 9 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Joint Session for Brazillian President Jose Sarney, 1986 September (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Swearing in of New Members, 1986 November (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - House Leadership, Tip O'Neill, Jim Wright, 1986 Novemeber (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - "Face the Nation" with Trent Lott, Bob Dole, Leslie Stahl, 1986 December (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Arms Control Meeting, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty Signing, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Sister Mary Turley, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Luncheon, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - President Jimmy Carter and Werner Brandt, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Senator Robert Dole, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Receiving Clock Award, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Eastern Washington University President Alexander Shilt, circa 1987 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - National Cancer Institute's 50th Anniversary Awards, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Speaker Jim Wright's Trip to Spain and Russia, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - F.A.A. Members, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - March of Dimes Poster Child and House Leadership, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Representatives Michell and Broomfield, Senator Sarbanes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Representative Jamie Whitten, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Librarian of Congress Dr. Boorstin's Going Away Lunch, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Actors Fund Dinner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Washingtonian Magazine Photos, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Heather Foley with Dog, Alice, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Publicity Photos, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Irene Ringwood and Steve Wright, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Democratic Congressional Dinner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Representatives Michel, Natcher, and Whitten, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Greenbriar, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Spokane, Washington Junior High School, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Roanne Schneider, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Roanne Schneider and Joe Powell, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Roanne Schneider, Joe Powell, and Phil Swink, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Speaker Election, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - "Face the Nation" with Senator Phil Grahm, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - St. Patricks Day Party with President Ronald Reagan, 1987 March (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Phil Swink, Joe Powell, Werner Brandt, 1987 Spring (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Flag Day, with Justice William C. Goodloe, 1987 June (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - World Forum by American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1987 June (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - House Counsel Steve Ross, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Admiral Poindexter and Counsel at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Peter Rodino and Steve Ross at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Questioning Fawn Hall and Admiral Poindexter at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Questioning Lieutenant Colonel Oliver North at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Iran-Contra Committee Members in Senate Foreign Affairs Room, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Chairman Hamilton at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Senator Orin Hatch, Peter Rodino, etc. at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Heather Foley at Iran-Contra Hearings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Swearing in of CIA Director, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - "We the People" Event on the Capitol Steps, 1987 September 16 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Heather Foley at the Actors Fund Dinner, 1987 October (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Garrison Jr. High School in Walla Walla, Washington, 1987 October (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Presenting Excellence in Education Award at Garrison Jr. High School, Walla Walla, Washington, 1987 October (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Washington State Delegation at SCC Conference, 1987 October 7 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - National Safety Belt Use Day Event, 1987 October 15 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Heather Foley and Dog, Alice, 1987 November 12 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Representative Jack Brooks' Portrait Unveiling, 1987 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Representative Nick Rahall enroute to Greenbriar, 1987 Winter (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - National Grange Manager Ed Anderson, 1987 December (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - President Ronald Reagan, 1987 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Arms Control Leadership Awards, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Supreme Soviet Delegation and Dinner, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Tip O'Neill, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Larry Erickson, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Governor Michael Dukakis, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Governor Michael Dukakis, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Representative Frank Annunzio, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - President Ronald Reagan Speech (signed by Warren Burger), circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - House Leadership, Representatives Wright and Cohelo, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - House Leadership and Whips, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Speaker Jim Wright, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - McDermott, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Congressional Student Award Recipient Todd Kelley, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Swearing in of New Members, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - House Leadership, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Swearing in of Jim Billington as Librarian of Congress, with President Ronald Reagan, Justice Renquist, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Chief of Protocol, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Boy Scout Patriot Award, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Addressing Congress at Bicentennial, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Office Staff, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Representative Hal Daub, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Majority Whip Dinner for New Members, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Canadian Free Trade Agreement Bill Signing, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Washington State Democrats, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Ladybird Johnson, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Fishing at Chesapeke Bay with Representative Dyson, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Jesse Jackson, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Speaker Wright's Dinner for New Members, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - President Ronald Reagan, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Bob Michel Tribute, 1988 January (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Day of the State of the Union Address with President Ronald Reagan an Representative Coehlo, 1988 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - State of Union with President Ronald Reagan, 1988 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - State of Union with President Ronald Reagan (Signed), 1988 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Memorial Services for Representative Dan Daniel, 1988 January 26 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - President Ronald Reagan at Egyptian State Dinner, 1988 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - "Meet the Press" with Lieutenant General Colin Powell, 1988 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Postmasters, 1988 February (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - President of Sony, 1988 March (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - St. Patrick's Day Party with President Ronald Reagan, 1988 March (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Representative James Howard Funeral, 199 March 29 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - "Close-Up" Group, 1988 Spring (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Representative Dick Gephardt, 1988 Spring (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - White House Leadership Breakfast, 1988 April (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - "Most Respected Congressman" Awarded by Fleishman, Hillyard, Inc., 1998 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Washington Realtors, 1988 May (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - "Meet the Press" with Secretary of State Jim Baker, 1988 May 1 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Representative Nick Rahall, 1988 May (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - 5th Congressional District Art Show, 1988 May (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Interns and Pages, 1988 Summer (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Governor Michael Dukakis, 1988 June (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Farm Bureau Golden Plough Award, 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Congressional Barbecue with President Ronald Reagan, 1988 September (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - President Ronald Reagan at White House Meeting, 1988 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - "Political Advertising Package", LIMBI, Inc., 1988 December (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - New Members Dinner with Office Staff, 1988 December (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Portrait of President Ronald Reagan, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - President George H. W. and Barbara Bush, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Bobby Brett, Spokane Indians and Minor League Managers, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Representatives Dingell and Glickman, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Representative George Miller and Others, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - P.O.W. and M.I.A. Event, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - New Leadership, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - "This Week" with Representative Hyde, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial Stamp Event, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Speaker Presiding", circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Heather Foley with Vice President Dan Quayle, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - District Visit, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miya Iwataki and Bert Nakano, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Speaker Jim Wright's Portrait, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Spokesman Review", circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Speaker Jim Wright Passing on Gavel with Democratic Leadership, Representatives Gephard, Gray, and Bonior, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Signing National Defense Budget Bill, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Richard Bay, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Navy Officers, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Vice President Dan and Mrs. Quayle, Heather Foley, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Richard Bates, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Astronauts, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - National Rifle Association, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Gary Hymel of Hill and Knowlton Co., 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - American Mining Congress, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Werner Brandt's VIP Breakfast, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Robert Redford, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Swearing-In Day, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Representative Claude Pepper's Funeral, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Representatives Gephardt and Gray, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bicentennial Coin Stamping Event, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Golden Girls Delegation, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Jack Buckner, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Greenbrier Issues Conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Leadership Meeting with President George H. W. Bush at White House, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Colonel Foley, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Groundbreaking Event, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Wolpe, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Soviet Journalists, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - New Members 101st Congress, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Speaker Jim Wright's last press conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Abernathy, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Being Sworn In, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Representative Gejdenson's District, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Inauguration Ceremony, 1989 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Representative Brooks' Breakfast for New Members, 1989 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Washington Realtors Breakfast, 1989 April (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Costa Rican President Oscar Arias, 1989 April (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - "Meet the Press", 1989 April 2 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - "Meet the Press", 1989 June 18 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pages and Interns, 1989 Summer (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Representative Tony Coehlo, 1989 June 9 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Majority Whip Tony Coelho, Heather Foley, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "America: At Issue", 1989 July (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Representative Frank Annunzio and Delegation Honoring Foley, 1989 July (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Ways and Means Bicentennial Dinner, 1989 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Boris Kalyagin, Soviet TV, and Joel Seidman, USIA-TV, 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - White House Congressional Barbecue with President George H. W. Bush, 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Pages and Interns, 1989 Fall (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Washington State Centennial with President George H. W. Bush in Spokane, Washington, 1989 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Latvian Delegation, Pope Shenouda III, 1989 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - President George H. W. Bush, 1989 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Representative Martin Frost Dinner in Dallas, Texas, 1989 October (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - "Meet the Press" with Sentor Mitchell, 1989 October, 1 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - "Housing Now!" Rally for Homeless, 1989 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Washington State University, Cougar Reunion, 1989 November (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Bill Signing with President George H. W. Bush, 1989 November 17 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - President Jimmy Carter and Vice President Walter Mondale Delegation, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - President Jimmy Carter, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 64)